<resources>
    <string name="app_name" translatable="false">Kima</string>

    <string name="hello_blank_fragment" translatable="false">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="rules_dialog_title">Rules:</string>
    <string name="rules_dialog_close_btn_text">Close</string>
    <string name="btn_place_card_text">Play card</string>
    <string name="scoreboard_title">Scoreboard</string>
    <string name="scoreboard_round">Round</string>
    <string name="scoreboard_you">You</string>
    <string name="scoreboard_cpu">CPU</string>
    <string name="scoreboard_main_menu_button">Main menu</string>
    <string name="scoreboard_play_again_button">Play again</string>
    <string name="menu_title">Menu</string>
    <string name="points_text">POINTS</string>
    <string name="app_title">KIMA!</string>
    <string name="btn_start_game">Start game</string>
    <string name="btn_rule_text">Rules</string>
    <string name="btn_close_scoreboard">Close</string>
    <string name="btn_you_won_tricks_dialog">YOU WON!</string>
    <string name="btn_next_trick_dialog">Next trick</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="rules_dialog_into_text">\n\n<b>Playing rules</b>


\n\nBoth players start with five cards on their hand. You always get to play the first card, then the computer will try to play a better card than the one you played.

\n\nThe players always need to follow suit. If there are no cards of the same suit as the played card, any card may be played. The idea of the game is to take more tricks than the opponent.

\n\nTaking a trick means that you have the highest ranking cards of the two played cards. Or, that the first played card is of a suit than the other player does not have. Therefore, it is advantageous to have many cards of the same suit.

\n\nThe player who won the trick begins the next trick by playing a card.

\n\nIn the end, the points are counted and the player with the most points wins.

\n\n\n\n

<b>Game example:</b>\n\n

- You being and play the 6 of spades.\n
- The computer has no spades and therefore plays the 3 of diamonds.\n
- You take the trick, receives one poing and gets to start the next trick.\n
- You play the jack of diamonds.\n
- The computer plays the queen of diamonds. This card follows suit and as a higher rank.\n
- The computer takes the trick, receives one point and begins the next trick.\n
- The same procedure is repeated for all 5 cards on the hand.</string>
</resources>